https://www.movingscam.com/privacy-policy

Endorsed Movers List
You Load/We Drive Companies:
| Reviews
Full Services Moving Companies:
| Reviews
Auto Transport Companies:
Coast to Coast Auto - About
| Reviews
International Moving Companies:
General
Movingscam.com respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Web site or responds using our interactive forms. This privacy policy outlines the information Movingscam.com will collect and how we will use that information. This statement also will instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visitMovingscam.com Web site or respond to our advertisements.
Individually Identifiable Information
Movingscam.com will not collect any individually identifiable information about you such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address unless you provide it to us voluntarily.
If you do not want your individually identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the e-mail address listed at the bottom of this policy. We will delete your information from our existing files.
When you do provide us with individually identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways unless stated otherwise: we may store and process it to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; we may use it to contact you; and we may provide it to third parties.
Except as stated in this privacy policy or at the time of collection, user’s personally identifiable information, will not be transferred to a party outside Movingscam.com, its divisions, its vendors providing Internet hosting services or third party list managers unless stated at the time of collection.
Children
Movingscam.com has no intention of collecting any individually identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address from individuals under the age of 13. Where appropriate, Movingscam.com will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our Web site or in response to advertisements. If a child has provided us with individually identifiable information, that child’s parent or guardian should contact us at the e-mail address or phone number listed at the bottom of this policy if they would like this information deleted from our records.
Non-Individually Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not individually identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site or advertisement.
Information We May Place Automatically On Your Computer’s Hard Drive
When you view one of our Web sites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor a Web site or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
We do not control the privacy policies of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks. Movingscam.com users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.
Whom to Contact
If you have submitted individually identifiable information through a Movingscam.com Web site or interactive advertisement and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at privacy@movingscam.com. We will delete this information from our existing files.
Moving Company Reviews
Message Boards
Find a reputable mover
Home
About Us
Reviews
Articles
Message Boards
Copyright 2020 Movingscam.com. All Rights Reserved. Terms & Conditions.  Proudly Hosted by NuggetWeb.com.
